shohoz.com 2019-03-10

# Buy Bus Tickets Online | Bus Tickets | Privacy Policy : Shohoz.com

**Please Note: Tickets of Bangladesh Vs England ODI - III at Chittagong will be available in phases starting from 10:00 AM on 10th Oct 2016. To buy tickets,Click here**

**Please Note: Tickets of Bangladesh Vs England ODI - III at Chittagong will be available in phases starting from 10:00 AM on 10th Oct 2016. To buy tickets,Click here**

### Privacy Policy

We, at shohoz.com, ensure to maintain the highest standards of transactional security and quality so that your information and details are secure. To know more about our policies please read the following to learn about our information gathering and dissemination practices.

Note: Kindly note that our privacy policy is subject to change at any time without prior notice. To ensure that you are aware of any changes, please review this policy at regular intervals.

By visiting this website you agree to be bound by the terms and conditions of this Privacy Policy. Any disagreement will be subject to the jurisdiction of Dhaka, Bangladesh.

By mere use of the Website, you express consent to our use and disclosure of your personal information in accordance with this Privacy Policy. This Privacy Policy is incorporated into and subject to the Terms of Use

##### 1\. Collection of Personally Identifiable Information and other Information

When you use our Website, we store your browsing information so that we canprovide services and features that meet your needs,.

In general, you can browse the Website without telling us who you are or revealing any personal information about yourself. Once you give us your personal information, you are not anonymous to us. You always have the option to not provide information by choosing not to use a particular service or feature on the Website. We compile your usage behaviour and personal information and the information on an aggregate basus to internal research to better enhance our product offerings to serve you better.. This information may include the URL that you just came from (whether this URL is on our Website or not), which URL you next go to (whether this URL is on our Website or not), your computer browser information, and your IP address.

We use data collection devices such as "cookies (small file stored on your computer)" on certain pages of the Website to help analyse our web page flow, measure promotional effectiveness, and promote trust and safety. We offer certain features that are only available through the use of a "cookie".

Additionally, third parties may also place cookies or similar devices on our website, which we cannot control. If you choose to buy on the Website, we collect information about your buying behaviour.

If you transact with us, we collect some additional information, such as a billing address, a credit / debit card number and a credit / debit card expiration date and/ or other payment instrument details.If you post messages or leave a feedback for us, we will collect that information you provide to us. We retain this information as necessary to resolve disputes, provide customer support and troubleshoot problems as permitted by law.

If you send us personal correspondence, such as emails or letters, or if other users or third parties send us correspondence about your activities or postings on the Website, we may collect such information into a file specific to you.

We collect personally identifiable information (email address, name, phone number.) from you when you set up a free account with us. We do use your contact information to send you offers based on your previous orders and your interests. However, data protection is a matter of trust and your privacy is important to us. We shall therefore use your name and other information which relates to you in the manner set out in this Privacy Policy. We will only collect information where it is necessary for us to do so and we will only collect information

##### 2\. Sharing of personal information

We will only share personal information with companies, organizations or individuals outside the periphery of Shohoz.com if we have a good-faith and believe that access, use, preservation or disclosure of the information is reasonably necessary to:

  * meet any applicable law, regulation, legal process or enforceable governmental request.
  * enforce applicable Terms of Service, including investigation of potential violations.
  * detect, prevent, or otherwise address fraud, security or technical issues.
  * protect against harm to the rights, property or safety of Shohoz.com, our users or the public as required or permitted by law.

We may share aggregated, non-personally identifiable information publicly and with our partners – like bus operators, agents or connected sites. For example, we may share information publicly to show trends about the general use of our services. We may also share consolidated information provided by like-minded users with bus operators without ever taking individual names, email ids or other contact details.

If Shohoz.com is involved in a merger, acquisition or asset sale, we will continue to ensure the confidentiality of your personal information and give notice before personal information is transferred or becomes subject to a different privacy policy.

##### 3\. Security Precautions

Our Website has stringent security measures in place to protect the loss, misuse, and alteration of the information under our control. Whenever you change or access your account information, we offer the use of a secure server. As informed earlier in this policy, once we receive your information we ensure strict security guidelines to protect it against unauthorized access. For example, we use SSL security to protect users against identity theft & spyware.

##### 4\. Your Consent

By using the Website and/ or by providing your information, you consent to the collection and use of the information you disclose on the Website in accordance with this Privacy Policy, including but not limited to your consent for sharing your information as per this privacy policy.

We may decide to make amends to this privacy policy without prior information, therefore, it is suggested you review this page at regular intervals. This ensures you are up-to-date with the details of the information we collect, how we use it, and under what circumstances we disclose it.

Scroll

#### Available Bus Operators

* * *

  * Abdullah Paribahan
  * Agomony Express
  * Akota Transport
  * Al-Mobaraka Paribahan
  * Alhamra Paribahan
  * Barkat Travels
  * Chaklader Paribahan
  * Comfort Line Pvt Ltd
  * Dhaka Line
  * Diganta Express
  * Diganta Paribahan
  * Dipjol Enterprise
  * Elish Paribahan
  * Emad Enterprise
  * Ena Transport (Pvt) Ltd
  * Green Line Paribahan
  * Hanif Enterprise
  * HIMACHOL
  * Islam Paribahan
  * Kanak Paribahan Ltd
  * M M Paribahan
  * Manik Express
  * Nabil Paribahan
  * New S.B Super Deluxe
  * Ranga Provat Paribahan Ltd
  * Relax Transport Ltd.
  * Royal Coach
  * Rozina Enterprise
  * S.B Super Deluxe
  * S.R Travels (Pvt) Ltd
  * Sagorika Enterprise
  * Saintmartin Hyundai
  * Saintmartin Paribahan Ltd
  * Saintmartin Travels
  * Shahzadpur Travels
  * Sheba Green Line
  * Sheba Transport
  * Shohagh Paribahan
  * Shoukhin Paribahan
  * Shuvo Bosundhara Paribahan
  * Shyamoli Paribahan
  * Soudia Air Con
  * Soudia Coach Service
  * SP Golden Line
  * Star Line Special Ltd.
  * Tisha Group
  * Tuba Line
  * Tungipara Express
  * Year-71

#### Eid Tickets

* * *

#### How does it work?

  * **Login with Facebook** and refer your friends
  * When your friends buy tickets from Shohoz.com, you get Tk. 50 talktime
  * Your friends also get Tk. 200 off on their first purchase
  * 

  * Tickets booked for your journey between **05 Sep 16** and **17 Sep 16** are classified as **Eid Tickets**.
  * SMS tickets are not acceptable for Eid Tickets. **Please carry a printed ticket while travelling**.
  * **Green Line Paribahan** tickets are available through Call Centre. Please call: 16374

  * Buy bus tickets from Shohoz.com Android App & get discount upto **Tk. 300** on your first order.
  * Get discount upto **Tk. 150** second order ownards.

  * To buy your tickets for Eid travel with ease and convenience, you are advised to download the **Shohoz - Buy Bus Tickets** Android App from Google Playstore.

  * During Eid travel, bus operators reserve the right to **CANCEL / DELAY** trips or change BUSES / SEATS due to unavoidable reasons, which is beyond Shohoz.com's control.

  * **Please Note:** In case of trip cancellations during Eid, passengers are requested to claim the refund for their tickets from respective bus operators / counters.
